我最近都活在自己的腦袋裡面
I've been living in my mind for some time
以為你已經明白；跟我的罪行看開
thought that you had understood; made peace with my crimes
現在我坐在這邊，桌子空空
Now I'm sitting here with nothing on the table
又只有我的心跟靈魂
but my heart and my soul, again
每位小馬都
Everypony talks
談吐著渺小的夢
about their little dreams
但我還在追隨我丟下的心
but I'm still following the heart I left behind
現在我就是給怪
Now I'm the one to blame
全部倒在我頭頂
Just take it out on me
一直來都是這樣
It's always been this way
你看來還不知道
something you've never seen
所以全都怪我頭頂
So blame it on me
全部倒在我頭頂
Take it out on me
真希望你還記得
I wish that you'd remember
我仍是自己
that I'm still me
真希望你能還我清靜
I wish you'd leave me be
但請你就看我神情
but please just look at me
我不知道我想要什麼
Don't know what I want anymore
或自由的意義
or what it means to be free
噢，搞砸了，搞砸了，搞砸
Oh, fuck it up, fuck it up, fuck it up
請你管好自己
wish you could get a grip
Never been your coat
沒給你擦過屁股
你的，好嗎
And you, not mine
不懂就閉嘴
Just stay in your lane
我們就沒事
and we'll be just fine
There's more to life than magic
人生不只是魔法
but it keeps me feeling good
但魔法讓我開心
你沒什麼選擇
Pick your poison now
體驗我的過去
to stand where I've stood
給自己一點時間休息
Taking a moment to rest
試著清理好我的心
Clearing my mind of the mess
我已放棄
I surrender
所以全都怪我頭頂
So blame it on me
全部倒在我頭頂
Take it out on me
真希望你還記得
I wish that you'd remember
我仍是自己
that I'm still me
真希望你能還我清靜
I wish you'd leave me be
但請你就看我神情
but please just look at me
我不知道我想要什麼
Don't know what I want anymore
或自由的意義
or what it means to be free